<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>filippo.im</title>
    <link>https://filmauri.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on filippo.im</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://filmauri.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Personal thoughts \#1</title>
      <link>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/personal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/personal/</guid>
      <description>I find myself putting this thought in writing on a night seemingly like many others. What prompted me to talk about this is a chapter in &amp;ldquo;The Four Loves&amp;rdquo; by C.S.Lewis called Friendship.
With this return to less restrictive measures I am discovering again what is the root of a friendship, what truly makes me say: &amp;ldquo;These are my friends.&amp;rdquo; From a biological point of view, friendship is the least natural of affections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invisible influence</title>
      <link>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/post04/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/post04/</guid>
      <description>What causes us to make decisions in life? We think the answer is obvious. People know what&amp;rsquo;s good for them. They weigh their options and make a rational decision! When a waiter in a diner asks if you&amp;rsquo;d like to order dessert after a meal the answer is easy. My belly isn&amp;rsquo;t full + I love sweets = of course I&amp;rsquo;d like dessert! In other words, YOU make YOUR OWN decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One small step for an ape, one big step for humankind</title>
      <link>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/neuralink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/neuralink/</guid>
      <description>Can you play video games using your brain as a controller? The answer is yes
Neuralink, a company founded by Elon Musk in 2016, has recently been all over the news as it has managed to do something extremely fascinating.
In fact, they managed to get a monkey to play a video game, albeit a simple one compared to more modern video games. Well but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t end there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a site using HUGO</title>
      <link>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/tutorialsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/tutorialsite/</guid>
      <description>Want to have a site similar to mine without spending a dime? Do you want it a little more beautiful? Then you&amp;rsquo;re in the right place! A few days ago I had a few hours free during an afternoon and I wanted to try my hand at what I thought was one of the greatest feats in human history. Well, thank goodness, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t as hard as I thought it would be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://filmauri.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filmauri.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Libri in lettura  I quattro amori (C.S. Lewis) L&amp;rsquo;origine delle specie (Charles Darwin)  Libri da leggere  Bioetica (Adriano Pessina) Bunker Diary (kevin Brooks) Data and Goliath (Bruce Schneier) Dottor Jakyill and mr Hyde Entropia e Arte Evoluzione e libertà (Hans Jonas) How Not To Be Wrong (Jordan Ellenberg) I duellanti (Conrad) I problemi della filosofia (Bertrand Russel) Il Gene (Siddartha Mukherjee) Il morbo dei dottori. la strana storia di Ignac semmelweis L&amp;rsquo;abbraccio (Mikel Azurmendi) L&amp;rsquo;ordine del tempo (Carlo Rovelli) L&amp;rsquo;origine della specie (Charles Darwin) Le farò un po&#39; male (Adam Kay) Liftoff (Eric Berger) Life at the Speed of Light: The Doble Helix and the Dawn of Digital Life Molto forte, incredibilmente vicino (Foer) Non ti ho mai promesso un giardino di rose (Greenberg Joanne) Open (Andre Agassi) Regenesis: How Synthetic Biology will Reinvent Nature and Ourselves Se una notte di inverno un viaggiatore (Italo Calvino) Sulla traccia di Nives (Erri de Luca) The Hero Code: Lessons Learned from Lives Well Lived (Admiral William H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Films</title>
      <link>https://filmauri.github.io/movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filmauri.github.io/movies/</guid>
      <description>Films da vedere Film visti  Il gladiatore ⭐ 2001 Odissea nello spazio Interstellar ⭐ Gravity ⭐ The Martian Blade Runner Trilogia de &amp;ldquo;Il Signore degli Anelli&amp;rdquo; ⭐ Arrival Inception Dunkirk Memento Tenet ⭐ The Imitation Game La teoria del tutto ⭐ I pirati della Silicon Valley Revolution OS (documentario) La principessa Mononoke Porco Rosso La città incantata Il mio vicino Totoro Will Hunting, genio ribelle ⭐ Snowden ⭐  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first Post</title>
      <link>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/tg-gh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/tg-gh/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone!
I am writing this page not knowing what will become of this project.
I&amp;rsquo;m sure something will come to me though. What made me start this blog even though I didn&amp;rsquo;t really know what would become of it is the book: Start Now, Get Perfect Later by Rob Moore. I listened to the summary of it on 4books, a startup by Marco Montemagno, and it convinced me. The fundamental message is the one expressed in the title.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://filmauri.github.io/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filmauri.github.io/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
