<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on filippo.im</title>
    <link>https://filmauri.github.io/tags/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on filippo.im</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://filmauri.github.io/tags/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The evolution of Right and Wrong</title>
      <link>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/post08/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/post08/</guid>
      <description>Are people born good and then corrupted by society or born bad and then made good by society?
This is the question that &amp;ldquo;The Goodness Paradox&amp;rdquo; by Richard Wrangham begins with.
This is more than just a philosophical question and many Religious people have different thoughts on it. Hobbes would say that we are all selfish and bad from birth, while Rousseau claimed that we were all born good. Scientists have tried to answer this question by giving ethic tests to infants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal thoughts \#2</title>
      <link>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/personal1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/personal1/</guid>
      <description>Again, I am writing during a night like many others. Unlike the last &amp;ldquo;Personal Thoughts&amp;rdquo; this thought of mine originated from nothing other than what I am experiencing.
It is impossible that at this moment in history a person does not have an impelling desire for life. I feel an immense tension towards life, towards action and sharing. The need, the desire fights against nothingness, against skepticism. In this moment in Italy the situation is fairly quiet in terms of contagions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal thoughts \#1</title>
      <link>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/personal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/personal/</guid>
      <description>I find myself putting this thought in writing on a night seemingly like many others. What prompted me to talk about this is a chapter in &amp;ldquo;The Four Loves&amp;rdquo; by C.S.Lewis called Friendship.
With this return to less restrictive measures I am discovering again what is the root of a friendship, what truly makes me say: &amp;ldquo;These are my friends.&amp;rdquo; From a biological point of view, friendship is the least natural of all affections.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
