<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Science on filippo.im</title>
    <link>https://filmauri.github.io/tags/science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Science on filippo.im</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://filmauri.github.io/tags/science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The evolution of Right and Wrong</title>
      <link>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/post08/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/post08/</guid>
      <description>Are people born good and then corrupted by society or born bad and then made good by society?
This is the question that &amp;ldquo;The Goodness Paradox&amp;rdquo; by Richard Wrangham begins with.
This is more than just a philosophical question and many Religious people have different thoughts on it. Hobbes would say that we are all selfish and bad from birth, while Rousseau claimed that we were all born good. Scientists have tried to answer this question by giving ethic tests to infants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding ET</title>
      <link>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/post07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/post07/</guid>
      <description>A huge amount of data made available to anyone who wants to look for possible alien signals: if there is an ET hiding among us, we will find it.
  Breakthrough Listen   The Breakthrough Listen Initiative has recently published the report of the most comprehensive survey ever conducted on radio emissions from the Milky Way and in particular from the region around the black hole at the center of our galaxy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Multiverse</title>
      <link>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/post06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/post06/</guid>
      <description>The universe we live in could be very large but limited or it could be infinitely large.
Physicist Brian Greene says that if the second option is the true one then so is something else: there are so many ways matter can organize itself within that infinite universe. But, in the end, matter must repeat itself and organize itself in similar ways. So, if the universe is infinitely large, it is also home to infinite parallel universes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News from Space</title>
      <link>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/post05/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/post05/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard of Perseverance, the NASA rover that landed on Mars on February 18. Along with it came a small drone called Ingenuity that made history on April 19. In fact, never before that day had a craft managed to hover over another planet. Due to the distance from Mars, scientists monitoring the drone had to wait more than 3 hours to get the data from the experiment. Such a great distance in fact does not allow the flying of the drone, even the transmitted light reflected from Mars takes tens of minutes to reach us.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
