<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on filippo.im</title>
    <link>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on filippo.im</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://filmauri.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>One small step for an ape, one big step for humankind</title>
      <link>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/neuralink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/neuralink/</guid>
      <description>Can you play video games using your brain as a controller? The answer is yes
Neuralink, a company founded by Elon Musk in 2016, has recently been all over the news as it has managed to do something extremely fascinating.
In fact, they managed to get a monkey to play a video game, albeit a simple one compared to more modern video games. Well but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t end there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a site using HUGO</title>
      <link>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/tutorialsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/tutorialsite/</guid>
      <description>Want to have a site similar to mine without spending a dime? Do you want it a little more beautiful? Then you&amp;rsquo;re in the right place! A few days ago I had a few hours free during an afternoon and I wanted to try my hand at what I thought was one of the greatest feats in human history. Well, thank goodness, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t as hard as I thought it would be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first Post</title>
      <link>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/tg-gh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filmauri.github.io/posts/tg-gh/</guid>
      <description>Chiunque abbia ricevuto questo link si ritenga fortunato! Finalmente sono riuscito a caricare questo sito e da ora comincierò a scrivere cose interessanti riguardo alla mia vita, cose che faccio o che succedono nel mondo. Appena riesco farò una sezione Libri nella quale ci saranno tutti i libri che ho letto a partire dall&amp;rsquo;inizio della prima quarantena e quelli che mi sono detto che dovrò leggere.
Spero che questo progetto non finisca nel dimenticatoio tra 5 giorni!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
